{
	"db": [
		{	
			"id": 1,
			"question": "Мне следовало сделать это вчера.",
			"answer": "I should have done it yesterday",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 2,
			"question": "Тебе следовало пойти туда.",
			"answer": "You should have gone there.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 3,
			"question": "Тебе следовало принять его предложение.",
			"answer": "You should have taken his offer.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 4,
			"question": "Мне бы стоило последовать его совету.",
			"answer": "I should have followed his advice.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 5,
			"question": "Мне бы стоило послушать его.",
			"answer": "I should have listened to him",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 6,
			"question": "Мне следовало понять это намного ранее.",
			"answer": "I should have understood it much earlier.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 7,
			"question": "Тебе следовало купить ту квартиру.",
			"answer": "You should have bought that flat.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 8,
			"question": "Тебе следовало пойти туда с ней.",
			"answer": "You should have gone there with her.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 9,
			"question": "Им следовало начать изучать английский раньше.",
			"answer": "They should have started learning English earlier.",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		},
		{	
			"id": 10,
			"question": "Так хорошо наконец встретиться с вами лично!",
			"answer": "It's so good to finally meet you in person!",
			"tag": "",
			"difficulty": ""
		}
	]
}


